My Christmas Dream is a tv movie, romance, comedy film directed by James Head.
A department store manager sets out to create an amazing
holiday display window to impress the owner.
She asks a recently-fired employee to help her make the display, and
as they work together, they start to fall in love.
Christina, played by Danica McKellar.
Kurt, played by David Haydn-Jones.
Victoria, played by Deidre Hall.
Henry, played by Bruce Dawson.
Holly, played by Christine Lee.
Cooper, played by Christian Convery.
White Christmas is a 1954 American Christmas musical film directed by Michael Curtiz
and starring Bing Crosby, Danny Kaye, Rosemary Clooney, and Vera-Ellen.
Filmed in Technicolor, it features the songs of Irving Berlin, including a new version of the
title song, "White Christmas", introduced by Crosby in the 1942 film Holiday Inn.
Produced and distributed by Paramount Pictures, the film is notable for being the first to be released in VistaVision, a widescreen process developed by Paramount that
entailed using twice the surface area of standard 35mm film; this large-area negative was also used to yield finer-grained standard-sized 35mm prints.
The film explores themes of department store, single father, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.